The Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue UP170
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue
1951 -- 1963
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Forsyth School for Dental Hygenists
UP170
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Catalog of the Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists.
Biographical / Historical
The Forsyth School for Dental Hygenists, the second school of its kind in the country, was established in 1916, and its first class was graduated in September, 1917. In 1949, the school has became affiliated with Tufts University. It's not clear when the Forsyth School severed its connections with Tufts. Since 2002, the Forsyth School has been affiliated with the Massachusetts College of Pharmacy and Health Sciences.
- The Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1951 -- 1963; UP170.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Catalog of the Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1951 -- 1952; UP170.001.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.37 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1952 -- 1953; UP170.001.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.2 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1953 -- 1954; UP170.001.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.1 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1954 -- 1955; UP170.001.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.9 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1956 -- 1957; UP170.001.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.1 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1957 -- 1958; UP170.001.001.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.23 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1958 -- 1959; UP170.001.001.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.28 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1959 -- 1961; UP170.001.001.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.93 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists Catalogue, 1961 -- 1963; UP170.001.001.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.46 Megabytes (Box 1)